Oh, I am so excited for stewie's first play.
Don't you think it's a little soon...
For a musical about terri schiavo?
Or too late?
Shh, it's starting.
Hi, doctor, it's me-- michael schiavo.
- How's my wife doing?
- She's a vegetable.
I hate vegetables.
Don't worry about her, mr. Schiavo.
She's being kept alive by medical science.
Gee, look at all this stuff.
How does it all work?
Well, I'll tell you.
...
Oh, my god, here comes jared.
Wow, he's in kindergarten.
Hey, so you're the plug this year?
Hey, jared.
Yeah, I'm the plug.
Yeah, I was the plug three years in a row.
Like I don't know that?
Everybody knows that, jared.
Well, listen, don't you try
to be a jared plug, all right?
You just go out there,
you be the best stewie plug you can.
I sure will, jared.
Hey, you got any gummi bears on you?
No.
It'd be a lot cooler if you did.
You know, they say don't meet your heroes,
But they can eat my ass,
because that was awesome!
I don't know, don't you think...
It's kind of weird that
he's in kindergarten...
And he's still hanging around kids our age?
Hey, we are very lucky.
oh, here I go.
there he is.
Quick, peter, grab the video camera.
All right, all right.
What's wrong with stewie?
I think he has stage fright.
I think he has stage fright, peter.
That's what I just said, I said that.
Peter : Look at stewie.
What a baby.
Aw, no way.
Hey, chris, look, is that richard dreyfuss?
Oh, for crying out loud.
Hey, dreyfuss, where you going?
Get back here.
Dreyfuss, what are you doing here in quahog?
My nephew's in the play.
God, can't you go anywhere these days...
Without these damn paparazzi?
Where you going?
Oh, you going to the bathroom?
You going to have a close
encounter of the turd kind?
Hey, I think you're going
to need a bigger boat.
These jokes are for you, peter,
When you watch this tape in the future.
Hi, future peter.
I'm going to plant a tree
for you when I get home.
Look outside and you'll see a grown tree.
I'm going to plant a tree
for you when I get home.
Look outside and you'll see a grown tree.
Eeeeeee!
Now look at your hand.
It's just a nub, 'cause I'm
gonna cut off all the fingers.
Oh, yeah, past peter?
Well, two can play that game.
Take that.
Uh, wait a minute.
How was your bowel movement, peter?
Eh, I got some, but I
didn't get the troublemaker.
Wait, what time is it? I got to turn on
tmz.
Rene russo got a little
hot under the collar...
When we caught up with her
outside her home in the hills.
Rene, what was it like working
with douglas fairbanks?
Is it true you were born in 1880?
This is my rassinfrackin' land,
and I don't care what no man...
From no tennessee valley
authority says, consarnit!
Why are we watching tmz?
I hate this show.
Keep watching.
So what do you got?
I got richard dreyfuss
coming out of the bathroom...
At his nephew's play in rhode island.
Richard, hey, richard.
Hey, can I get your autograph?
fine.
Do you have a pen and paper?
What do I look like, a staples?
I don't carry that stuff around.
Look, I'm sorry, I can't help you.
Oh, what, you too big and
famous to walk over...
To that corner drugstore and
pick up a pen and paper...
And possibly some other groceries I need...
And come back and sign
several things for me?
You're a jerk.
That was my tape, everybody.
I sent that in and they put it on tv,
Which makes me a famous journalist.
Journalist? You're badgering a celebrity...
And passing it off as news.
Yeah, journalist.
And I got a hundred bucks for it,
Which I used to buy this $4,
000 video camera.
Meet peter griffin, video paparazzi.
From now on I'm gonna be
right where the action is,
Like my uncle "the guy in
the white hat" griffin.
Stewie, stewie, how's that oatmeal?
Is it true you're having an
affair with that oatmeal?
What do you say about the rumors...
That you have a full diaper?
I'm just trying to eat here.
What did you do to your mother's vagina?
Leave me alone!
How come your feet are so small?
Is it true you can't say "spaghetti"?
What about the rumors that you have cooties?
Is it true you doubled your
weight in the last six months?
Daddy, help me, daddy!
I can't get involved 'cause of journalism.
Tom, tom tucker, tom!
The news isn't funny.
It's not supposed to be funny.
Tom, who were you having
dinner with in there?
Was it a guy? Are you gay?
Someone said you were gay.
It was me.
Are the rumors I'm making up true?
Ignore me if you're gay.
Mayor west, over here.
What hot spot are you going
to this Friday night?
Oh, I've got some pretty nifty plans,
My camera-wielding friend.
Yeah? That's right.
Every Friday night,
I'm a clearance sale area rug.
Boy, I hope somebody buys me.
I'd look swell in their den.
Aw.
Ollie williams, why do you
look so much like will smith?
Hey, will smith,
What was it like to punch
that alien in the face?
Eddie murphy, what was that whole thing...
With you and that transvestite hooker?
Bernie mac, how come you died?
Oprah, why are you so fat, don cheadle?
You almost done in there, peter?
Hang on, lois-- stupid ollie
williams broke my glasses.
I got to put in my contacts.
By the way, the repair shop called.
They said they can't fix your camera.
Well, that's just great, lois, that's great.
And here I was going to use the money...
To take you to "can-cun" this winter.
Canc?n, peter.
Whoa, whoa, I don't like
ollie any more than you do,
But we are a 21st-century family,
And I will not have that kind of talk here.
Whatever.
Griffin, did you call the distributor...
About the...?
What, what's the problem?
okay, look, I know I was watching tv,
But I'll, I'll stay late.
No, that's not it, griffin.
There's, there's something
different about you.
You're not wearing glasses.
Yeah, they got busted; I'm wearing contacts.
I can see your eyes and,
and your eyelashes--
They're beautiful.
Who cares? What gives?
Griffin, I never noticed you before.
I like what I see.
Uh, okay.
Oh, no, I dropped my pencil.
Oh, I'll get it for you.
Yeah, this is gonna...
Work out just fine.
Excuse me.
Family, we need to talk.
Your father was sexually
harassed at work today.
What?
That's right.
Angela grabbed my ass.
So what?
Peter, a woman can't sexually harass a man.
Why not?
I don't know, it just
doesn't make any sense.
I mean, guys like being touched by women.
It's not harassment if you like it.
But I didn't like it.
I got sexually harassed at school.
My chemistry teacher, mr.
Taylor, rubbed my shoulders...
For 35 minutes in class the
one day I didn't wear a bra.
See, peter, that's harassment.
An older man, a weak, younger woman.
He could have taken advantage of her,
Forced her to do things to him.
He did-- awful things.
See?
But you, it just can't happen.
Griffin, get in here,
And make sure you have on your new uniform.
Why am I the only one who
has to wear denim shorts?
Because you're the only one
who looks this good in them.
Damn, griffin, you fill those out nicely.
Why is there a dusty gas station...
And a diet pepsi machine in your office?
'cause your car broke down, and you need...
To wipe a cold soda on
your neck to cool off.
Well, may-maybe I don't need to cool off.
Maybe you don't need to be employed.
It's hot in here, isn't it?
Yes.
You need to cool off, don't you?
I need to cool off.
You need to wipe your
neck with the soda can.
I need to wipe my neck with the soda can.
Do it!
Now, get out of here, you slut.
Okay. Can I keep the soda?
Oh, all right.
Yeah!
Ohhh...
Oh, god.
I really hope there's a
hungry horse back there.
Hello?
Oh, hi, angela, hang on.
Peter, it's your boss.
I don't want to talk to her.
She's gonna harass me.
Oh, don't be such a baby.
I'm sorry, angela, peter can't talk.
He's upstairs in the shower...
Touching himself to your picture.
Gimme that. Why are you calling me at home?
I want to hear you breathe.
Breathe into the phone for me,
griffin. What?
Shh, shh, shh. Don't talk, just breathe.
It turns me on.
That's it, griffin.
Keep breathing. God, I'm almost there.
Your breath is filling me up.
I like kangaroos.
Oh, sure you do.
Well, tomorrow, I'm getting
you a kangaroo t-shirt.
And she wants me to come
over to her house tonight...
To work on a "special project."
I know she's gonna make
me have sex with her.
What the hell am I gonna do?
I don't know, peter.
If you have sex with her,
you give her all the power.
If you don't have sex with her, you're gay.
You can't win.
I don't want to get fired...
And have to look for another job.
What the hell do I do?
I might be able to help you, peter.
All right, hurry up,
let's get this over with.
All right, unbutton your
shirt and your pants.
That oughta do it. Okay, close up.
All right, let me get lined up right,
So she'll think it's you
she's having sex with.
Wow, that's really clever. Thanks.
And if you don't feel like doing lois later,
I can stick around.
Let's-let's just see how this goes.
- Hello, griffin.
- Hello, angela.
You know, angela,
I've been thinking about it,
And I want to have sex with you now.
Really? Giggity.
Yeah, but-but I want to just do it...
Through my zipper, all right?
I-I-I don't want to have
to take off all my clothes,
'cause I'm self-conscious...
About my congressman barney frank body.
Well, I suppose I can work with that.
Oh, yuck.
What do you say we go Into
the bedroom? Uh, yeah, sure.
Aw, she's so ugly.
I don't want to get in that.
Peter, I'm-I'm not gonna do it.
Deal's off. Deal's off.
No, it isn't! Yes, it is.
I'm gonna spread my legs,
and it'll be you doing it, not me.
You better not. I am.
I'm re-jiggering my position right now.
Oh, no, you don't!
What the hell is going on here?
Hi, angela, I'm peter's friend,
glenn quagmire.
Uh, thank you so much for
having me in your home.
And, um, I would have had sex with you,
But peter neglected to tell me...
That you are a complete dumpster fire.
some friend, huh?
Okay, all right, take it easy.
I am tired of playing games, griffin.
I mean, let's go. I have waited long enough.
I'm having sex with you right now.
No! I don't wanna!
Griffin, you have sex with me,
or you're fired.
Fine! Fire me!
I'm through bein' harassed by you!
You know, this is awful timing,
But I-I remembered part of
the reason I came over was...
'cause my cousin is lookin'
for a job at the brewery.
I'll-I'll just put his
r?sum? under the door.
- Gimme another one, horace.
- All right, but slow down, peter.
Or else I'm gonna have to get
that lady boss of yours...
To come in here and give you
a good shoe to the gift bag.
You know, keep you in line.
I'm just kiddin' ya, peter.
You'll find yourself a new job.
Tv announcer: We now return to robert
mitchum In a backhand for sally.
You're getting on that train with me.
I can't go with you. I just can't.
Okay, I'll go. Ow! I said I'd go.
Why'd you give me the back of your hand?
Because I love you.
Wow, I thought you had to be in the nba...
To hit a girl in the face.
But I guess anyone can.
Of course you can hit a girl in the face.
They have faces, don't they?
Are-are you talkin' to me, robert mitchum?
You bet your ass I am.
Look at you, you're pathetic.
What kind of a man gets fired by a broad?
A man with a female boss? Don't crack wise.
Listen, peter, somewhere along the line,
you got turned around.
You're a man.
And whaddaya think it means to be a man?
Um, it means not gettin' pushed around.
Exactly. It means drinkin'...
Not because I want to,
but because I need to.
Right! It means standing up to fart,
Not hidin' it in a pillow,
Or holdin' it in till your stomach goes...
Now you've got it!
Gimme my keys, horace!
I'm going to see my boss!
But, peter, you're drunk!
Horace?
You're right. This is more important.
Angela!
Open up in there!
Oh, my god!
Angela!
Angela, wake up! What the-- griffin?
Angela, what the hell are you
doin' tryin' to kill yourself?
Oh, why the hell did you
pull me out of there?
You shoulda just left me alone!
That's how I'm gonna end up, anyway.
What are you talkin' about?
I'm talking about the fact...
That I have nothing to live for.
Sure, you do.
Someday, a white man's gonna
be elected president again.
Griffin, I haven't been
with anyone in ten years.
And when you spurned my advances,
It was a wakeup call.
No one's ever gonna love me again.
Wait a minute.
So that's why you been actin'
like such a wacky ass around me?
It's been so long since
I've been with a man,
I don't even remember what it feels like.
I always imagined it felt very painful.
You just sorta grit your teeth
and let us do what we want.
I just wish one person was
able to find me attractive.
That's not too much to ask, is it? - No...
Look, angela, I came
over here to punch you...
And maybe kick you in the boob.
But now I'm all turned around.
Angela?
Angela?! Right here.
But now all I want to do is help you out.
I'll tell you what, you know that ritzy,
Upscale place over on third?
The stuffy fella? That's it.
You be at the stuffy fella
tonight around 9:00.
I think I know someone who
might be perfect for you.
Mmm, well, hello.
Good evening, sir.
I am reginald new york
knickerbocker, millionaire.
Are you serving fish this evening?
No, sir.
Then I believe my guest has arrived.
There she is! You must be angela.
Hi, are you peter's friend, reginald?
Mmm, indeed I am.
Mmm, what a beautiful shade
of lipstick on those teeth.
Oh, thank you, but that's
just my gums bleeding...
From aggressive gingivitis.
Mmm, well, your mouth is too sweet...
For your teeth to want to stay in.
Oh. Yes.
Well, I-I'm just gonna
go to the powder room...
And freshen up.
She's eatin' it up.
This is easier than an american
finding his brother in china.
Ron?
Ron, where are you?
Over here, paul!
Oh, good, there you are.
It's pretty here.
Yes, it is.
Mmm, what a wonderful dinner.
Would you like some dessert?
Did you bake a pie? Well, there is a pie.
It's been baking since I met you.
Mmm, gross. What?Nothing.
You know, angela, there's
something I need to tell you.
My doctor has given me 24 hours to live.
Oh, my god!
No, no, it's quite all right.
Because I vowed to myself That I would
spend the last night of my life...
In the company of the most
beautiful woman in the world.
And that's just what I have done.
Oh, reginald. No, no, no.
This is already a perfect
end to a perfect evening.
Good night, my dear. Reginald...
I want you to make love to me.
Oh, if only I could,
But I must to a jew to
put my affairs in order.
I know what's going on here.
You don't want to be with me.
You're just like everybody else.
So-so go, then.
I'm just gonna stay here and kill myself.
But you can't kill yourself...
Every time somebody won't sleep with you.
I won't.
Just sleep with me just this once,
And it'll give me everything I need.
Sleep with me tonight.
Save my life.
Oh, that was fantastic!
It was exactly what I needed.
Mmm, well, hopefully there'll
be no more talk of suicide.
Oh, no. I feel better
than I've felt in years.
I have my confidence again.
I'm ready to go back out
there and meet someone.
Well, I'm glad to be of service.
Oh, just one more thing before you go.
What's that, my dear?
See you at work on Monday, griffin.
Huh? Oh, I'm gonna have to have a word...
With rite-aid about this fake moustache.
Well, I got my job back,
angela's happy again,
And she's not gonna harass me anymore.
Everything worked out perfect.
Not really, peter.
Yeah, you cheated on your wife.
No, I didn't. I used mort.
Oh, my god, I forgot about mort!
I want my two dollars!
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru